This is how I turned $200 into $2,200
from Messi scoring a goal at the World
Cup. Also guys, I have a free course in
the bio if you guys want to check it
out. It's pretty much explaining how to
get started. There's like 12 videos in
there and then I have a $100 package
pretty much just explaining everything
that you need to know when trading meme
coins. It's like 40 plus videos on
there, like hours of material. So, if
you guys really want to get into it,
definitely recommend you guys check
those out and yeah. So, I'll be honest,
a $2,200 P&L happens pretty often, so
it's nothing crazy, but turning three
sole, which is like a couple hundred
bucks, 200 bucks, into $2,500 is the
part where it gets a little tricky cuz
you need to hold longer and identify
what makes a coin actually run. And the
coin that I'm going to be showing you
guys today, you guys are going to be
super familiar with. His name is Messi.
He ended up scoring twice in the World
Cup. You know, the World Cup is a main
event. Everyone has their eyes on it.
So, obviously there's going to be a lot
of coins on it because meme coins are
pretty much just attention tokens. Like
it's whatever everyone is looking at.
So, I guess we'll hop straight into it.
I'm going to show you guys my vision,
what made me take this trade, and why I
was super bullish on it to hold it for
more than like a 10x. Now, obviously my
strategy is pretty much a scalping coin.
So, I kind of had a vision on this coin.
I knew that it would go above like 60,
70k. And so, that's why I held most of
my supply till then. Let's actually go
to the coin right now. By the way, if
you guys aren't using Terminal yet, I'm
going to be putting my ref in the
description. If you use my ref, you're
going to have discounted fees. So,
compared to Axiom, all these other
platforms, you're actually going to have
the lowest fees on Terminal. And so,
that basically just means more money for
you guys. So, check out my ref in the
description. Let's get straight into it
though. I'm going to give you guys a
little bit of context going into this
coin. It's the World Cup. Argentina is
playing against whatever other team or
whatever team Messi plays on. I don't
even know what team he plays on, but you
know, there's always the debate that
Ronaldo is better than Messi or Messi is
better than Ronaldo. Messi scoring a
goal in the World Cup is obviously a
huge deal because Ronaldo hasn't scored
any and if he scores two goals total in
the World Cup, he will be the first
person in the World Cup to score the
most amount of goals. And so obviously
this is a huge deal when, you know, the
biggest debate is Ronaldo or Messi. And
him scoring two goals in the World Cup
finals is obviously going to bring a lot
of attention and people are going to
call him like the goat or whatever,
right? They're going to think like, oh,
this settles the debate. Messi scored
two goals in finals. He's the first
person to score this many goals in
finals and he did it on one game. Like
everyone's going to be tweeting about
it. This is going to go super viral. And
so as soon as I saw this tweet right
here, I was a little bit late to it as
you can see. I had couple of my friends
buy before. Theo really good trader,
Shower really good trader, and then I
ended up buying a little bit later
because I was looking at a different
coin. So I'm going to pull up the tweet
right now. I'm just going to show you
guys like a baseline of what it said
pretty much. Lionel Messi broke like
three records today. One of them being
him scoring the most goals obviously,
the most matches played by someone, the
most World Cup matches played by anyone,
and yeah, he pretty much just made
history by scoring those two goals and
everyone was saying he was the goat. And
so as soon as I saw that tweet of Messi
breaking the record of all time while
being in his 38s and the debate of
Ronaldo or Messi still going on, I'm
like, I had a vision in my head and this
is super super important especially for
newer guys and even still established
people like me. It is super important to
have a thesis on why a coin should
actually run or not. This is something
that I've been doing pretty often
recently is I'll just be in my VC with
my friends and I will instantly buy a
coin and discuss on why I think it's
going to go higher. This will just help
you like think of a certain market cap
that it's going to go to and start
selling around that range. So you're not
just like blindly selling, you know, if
you're up 20%, 30%, like you kind of
have an idea of where the coin is going
to go. And so yeah, I bought this coin,
instantly started thinking, okay, this
is the World Cup, the most popular event
like in in world. And so instantly what
I did was I went to go check X to see if
it was actually trending, even though it
was like 5 minutes after. I went to my
trending page. This happened not even 2
minutes after Messi was number one
trending worldwide. Literally on the
top, he was number one trending in the
entire world. And so, as soon as I saw
that, this is the angle I was going for,
Messi ultimately wins the debate of who
is better, Ronaldo or Messi. And I was
like, okay, in my head, everyone is
going to tweet this. We had ChatGPT
literally tweet a picture of him as the
goat. Like, you know, it was pretty
obvious. Like, you you you could see it.
It's obvious it's always obvious in
hindsight, but like having a thesis
early on, before all these accounts
start posting, you're going to be
earlier than like 80% of the traders,
you know, buying at 50K, 60K. And that's
why I love my strategy. That's why I
love buying early because I'm able to
see the vision before anyone else
because I form a thesis on my own. And
so, yeah, I ended up buying the coin
right here with around three SOL. Three
SOL is 220 bucks. I had a vision to 50,
60K minimum. And so, as soon as I saw
Cobie buying at like 15K, I was like,
holy yeah, this [__] is probably going
to go. Some of my friends were in with
me. I had Alex Cook, another really good
trader. He was selling up here at 34K.
But honestly, I really like the way the
chart was moving. You know, once you
trade every single day for like 10, 12
hours, which is what I'm doing, I'm
trading 10, 12 hours, I kind of know how
charts move. And so, as soon as I saw
the chart moving like this, and then as
I see the chart moving like this, I see
tweets on the side of my screen like,
oh, this settles the debate, Messi is
the goat. I'm like, okay, this is just
proving my thesis. As soon as I saw the
volume coming in, I was like, okay,
maybe I should rethink my thesis here.
Like, how viral like will this go? And
so, I literally went to my Twitter. I
remember this. It's it's probably still
going on right now. I literally went to
my Twitter, searched up Messi, went to
latest. Even now, 5 seconds, 8 seconds,
8 seconds, there's tweets every 5 sec
every every every second almost right
now. And I imagine when he scored that
goal, there were tweets like probably
like 10 tweets every second and it was
just crazy to see because, you know, we
don't get events like the World Cup
often. So, it's just like it pretty much
just like confirmed my idea of like,
"Okay, this is going to go insanely
viral. I'm super early. I had the thesis
early on. Might as well hold and let all
the Twitter accounts just keep posting
it while I'm just in the coin and have
it gain virality for me." Like right
here, you could see goat. It was just
obvious in hindsight looking back at it
now, even though I did have the thesis.
So, as soon as I saw Cubsi buy right
here, I got instantly bullish. I was
like, "Okay, he broke it out." Bought
with like 10 sol, which is pretty
honestly a good amount at like 15k. So,
I decided to hold it a little bit extra
longer. And then right here, once I saw
this wallet buy, his name is [__] a
really, really good wallet. The coin
usually just shoots up whenever he buys,
but obviously the chart was already
instantly going up, you know, Cubsi
already bought it. The coin was pretty
much like 3x before he bought it. So, he
didn't have the craziest wick, but even
having that wallet, you know, there's
like tiers of wallets. There's like my
wallet, you know, Senad, Cubsi, all
these other KOLs and then there's like
higher tier wallets that like will break
out the chart with like a lot of sol
like this guy, [__] You know, you have
Pow, you have Cake. Those traders aren't
as active as of now, but you know,
there's always like these other small
people. Like it's new wallets every
time. Like now there's Domin, another
KOL that's loading in. Like there's new
KOLs that just like take over that role,
you know, people change play styles. And
so, seeing [__] buy up here at like
40k, honestly got me pretty bullish. At
this point, I think I had around like 15
sol or like 16 sol over here. And by the
way, ignore this 23. The reason why it's
23 is because if you go to my
transactions, I bought like 20 more
after, but ended up going break even
with it. So, so yeah, started getting
some sells off at 40k. You know, my
friend was also selling, but I also did
not want to clip too much supply because
I knew that it would just gain virality
and it would it might just take a second
for people to understand like this is
the biggest debate in the world. Messi
pretty much cleared his name in like one
debate, in my opinion in my eyes and in
everyone else's eyes. And so I I I knew
I was super early to this, but I also
wanted to take some profits. So I ended
up clipping like six SOL around here,
which was I think a good amount of my
size. Yeah, so I'm looking back at it
now. I actually had around 17 SOL when I
started clipping here, which is honestly
not bad because just to play the safe
game, you know, there's coins that just
randomly end up dying uh for no reason.
It's like it's honestly in this market
it's hard to tell what runs. And so you
really need to have a solid thesis. You
really need to like be trading 10 to 12
hours a day and even then you will have
the wrong thesis sometimes, which is
normal because it's meme coins, it's a
volatile game, you know, people buy,
people sell. Some people don't like
holding forever, so yeah, ended up
taking some profits here, took six SOL
and then went up to 50K, I took a little
bit extra two SOL at this point. I had
like 14 SOL in the coin. And going from
14 SOL to 30 SOL it means I would have
to hold it all the way from here to an
additional 2X, which is what I did. But
I'll show you guys. This is super
important going into this next part
because even though I sold a lot of
supply here, I think I was selling like
15, 20, 15, 15% here. I'll show you why
it's super important to have like small
percentage clips. So right here we had
another really good wallet called Remus.
Remus is obviously on this board with
the goat wallets, you know, these
wallets just have motion and so whenever
they buy the coin it'll obviously just
like go up because they're really good
traders, that's just how it works, okay?
So yeah, Remus bought obviously has copy
traders, he has people that just get
conviction just from seeing him buy. And
so the coin obviously went pretty high.
Soon as I saw him buy, I saw Go Eem and
his wallet in and I was like, okay, I
should probably start selling in smaller
increments now because this can go a lot
more crazier than I'm imagining. Ended
up selling another two and a half Solana
here at 60K and just holding through all
of this. This is a one-second chart, so
if I go to like the five-second chart,
this is like 40 seconds right here of me
holding. All this right here is about
three minutes maybe, three minutes of me
holding. Ended up holding through most
of this chop, you know, a lot of people
don't like doing technical analysis on
meme coins, but honestly for me it just
kind of keeps me in the loop of like
where I should be buying, where I should
be selling at. And so, whenever I see it
like dip heavily like into support like
this, I'm like, "Okay, I probably
shouldn't be panic selling. Like this is
a normal range where to like consolidate
at." And which is exactly what it did,
so held through all of it, waited for a
breakout, and that is exactly what
happened. It broke out of here, had a
fat wick. Someone bought 20 soul to
break it out, so being these wicks in
the chart obviously gets me bullish. But
of course, I need to take profits on the
way up. I don't like diamond handing. I
personally don't think you should
diamond hand a coin unless you have a
very, very strong thesis and you're like
in your mind you're like, "Okay, this is
going there." and you're positive. Other
than that, I think it's a great idea to
take profits along the way. It's the
smart thing to do. You should never
round trip this into a loss if you're in
my shoes, personally. But, you know,
everyone's different. Some people like
diamond handing, do you. But, I
personally like taking profits on the
way up, and that's what I did. I took it
in small increments. I took a three soul
sell right here, and then I waited just
for another breakout. Ended up selling
like a little bit because I felt like
that that this breakout was like a
little weak. But at the same time, you
know, we went up pretty much only up
since 3K for like a couple minutes
straight, so it consolidating right here
didn't really mean too much, but I still
wanted to take a couple extra profits
because, you know, I was already up
[__] up 30 soul off a three soul buy,
you know, it's it's amazing profits, so
ended up clipping another two soul, four
soul here. I think I had around, let me
see how much I had left. Yeah, so
looking back at it now, I had 18 soul
left in the chart at 86K. What that
means is me selling a two soul right
here, 18, that would be like 10%. I sold
another 10% here, and then like a 20%
here just to be safe. And honestly, the
volume was just crazy on this coin. I'm
seeing my Twitter tracker blow up, so
obviously I kept holding and just
selling in increments. I was pretty much
one of the only key whales to catch this
coin. I think if I go to the top
traders, I'm fifth trader on this coin.
Theo, literally a [__] coho, bro. He
bought a lot at like 15k and ended up
making 53 SOL, so he mugged me. Leave it
at that. But yeah, sold one SOL here,
you know, we had another breakout over
here, started [__] going only up, and
then I sold another three SOL, you know,
selling in increments on the way up.
Think it's super important. Bought
another three SOL, two SOL. At this
point, the chart's at 120k. 120k in
these market conditions, trust me, it's
pretty good. And so yeah, I ended up
taking most of my profits here, which
was actually the top. So I did a really
good job at estimating, you know, what
this coin was going to go to, and that
is literally just because I had the
thesis on what I thought the coin would
run to, and I just had like a price in
mind, and I'm just playing it off
volume. That's super important, even if
you have a really good thesis. I mean,
you think a coin's going to go to this,
you know, that can change at any second
if, you know, a wallet buys or if
someone tweets it, anything can change
at any moment. And so that is the case
with the volume. I read the volume, I
knew that there was a lot of volume
going into this coin, the virality was
just going to keep getting more and more
bigger. And so that's why I ended up
holding most of my bag until 130. So
yeah, clipped a good bit over here, and
then once I saw it started breaking
down, pretty much went only down, broke
the support, whatever, went only down to
85k. And then at this point, I'm like,
okay, is this really going to get higher
than 120k? I didn't have that much in
the chart left. I had like five SOL, six
SOL. Yeah, so pretty much I felt like
the narrative started getting a little
exhausted, and then once it got to this
105k range, I was like, was checking out
my new pairs, whatever, and then I saw
another coin pretty much the exact same
narrative as Messi the Goat, just like a
different font or whatever. You know, a
PVP is what we call it. I thought 120
was a good range, and once I saw it go
lower, I was like, okay, I'm just going
to go with this coin. Boom, finished
with that coin, ended up [__]
securing that trade. This PNL is a
little off because I actually ended up
rebuying the coin when Chad GPT tweeted
that picture, as I showed you guys
earlier, of the goat. Yeah, this PNL's a
little bugged, but I ended up making up
31 SOL, I believe, on the dot. And so
going from $200 all the way to $2,400,
actually, now that I think about it,
it's pretty good, bro. I I think I
played this trade pretty pretty freaking
well. So, yeah guys, I hope you guys
enjoyed this video. Make sure you guys
use Terminal. If you're not already on
it, you are just missing out. You're
giving other platforms just more of your
fees when you could just be pocketing
that yourself. So,
Terminal, check it out in the
description. If you guys want to catch
me live, twitch.tv/mega. And let me know
what you guys thought of this video. And
I'll do more videos like this. And if
you guys have any recommendations, leave
them in the comments. If I see more than
like a couple people type the same
thing, you know, [__] it. I'll just rip
a video. Thank you guys for watching.
Catch you in the next one. Peace.